Now I'm going to introduce you to
现在 我将为你介绍
Jupyter notebooks. Notebooks are an amazing
Jupyter Notebook 这是一个
tool for data analysis, where text, code,
对数据分析来说很棒的工具
and images all sit in one document in your
文本、代码和图像都出现在你的浏览器的
browser.
同一个文档中
Here's an example notebook where I
这里有一个使用 notebook 的例子
explored predicting body fat percentage
我试着用它来预测身体脂肪百分比
with various regression models. Up top
利用各种回归模型
here you see what's called a text cell.
你看到最上面的就是文本单元 (text cell)
Cells are these guys and they can contain text
这些单元 (cell) 可以包含文本或者代码
or code. If I double-click on the text
如果我双击文本单元
cell, I can edit the text in here. It's
我可以在这里编辑文本
written in markdown, a text format with
它是用 markdown 语法格式写的
syntax that renders to HTML. So for instance,
可以渲染成 HTML
if I want to write a link, this is the
举个例子 如果我要写一个链接
syntax for it, and if I render the
它的语法是这样的 如果我渲染它
text, it's a link. This is a code cell.
它就是一个链接 这是一个代码单元
You can see here I'm importing some
你看我导入了一些库
packages like Numpy and Pandas. I can run
比如 Numpy 和 Pandas
this cell and the code is executed the
我可以运行它 单元里的代码就会被执行
same way as it is in the terminal or a
和终端或 Python 脚本里执行的方式一样
Python script. This command here
这一命令
"%matplotlib inline" will render images
%matplotlib inline 会渲染
generated with matplotlib in the
matplotlib 生成的图像
notebook instead of a separate window.
在 notebook 内部显示 而不是单独的窗口
If the cell returns some output, you see here.
如果单元有返回一些输出 你会在这里看到
For instance, data. head() returns an HTML
例如 data.head() 返回一个
table displaying some of the data. Right
显示部分数据的 HTML 表格
below here you see the data visualized
就在下面 这里 你看到可视化的数据
with a grid of scatter plots and
一个散点图的网格还有直方图
histograms. Notebooks even render math in
它甚至可以在文本单元中
a text cells.
渲染数学表达式
This is just an example of what you can
这只是你能用它做什么的一个例子
do with notebooks. You have your code,
你可以把代码 文档
documentation, visualizations, math, all in
可视化 数学表达式
one place.
都放在一个文档里
Next, I'll show you how to use notebooks
接下来 我将展示如何在你的工作流程中
in your workflow. It should take about an
使用 notebooks 这部分课程
hour to get through the lesson, so see
大约需要1小时
you in the classroom!
我们课堂上见